They say flowers fade and their beauty can't be weighed with flowers so fake
人们说鲜花不如假花美丽因为它们终将凋零
この世で造花より綺麗な花は無いわ
ゼイ セイ フラワーズ フェイド アンド ゼア ビューティー キャント ビー ウェイド ウィズ フラワーズ ソー フェイク
It's all because the way things are made live on lies that fabricate
但这都是因为它是依赖着虚假的谎言而被创造的
何故ならば総ては嘘で出来ている
イッツ オール ビコーズ ザ ウェイ シングズ アー メイド リブ オン ライズ ザット ファブリケイト
ANTIPATHY WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD
这虚伪的世界
アンティパシー ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド
WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD
ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド
WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD
ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド
WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD WORLD
ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド ワールド
ラルラルラ
ra ru ra ru ra
I'll raise, right away, my umbrella that will shade my body from rain
撑起了伞 仅仅因为它能遮蔽雨滴
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて
アイル レイズ ライト アウェイ マイ アンブレラ ザット ウィル シェイド マイ ボディ フロム レイン
Now dampened by the pain, can't escape, here my bangs and heart remain
但我却被疼痛所濡湿 无法逃脱 湿润的刘海和心脏一如既往留在这里
湿らす前髪とこころの裏面
ナウ ダンプンド バイ ザ ペイン キャント エスケイプ ヒア マイ バングス アンド ハート リメイン
All the TROUBLE I face
我面临的所有痛苦
煩わしいわ
オール ザ トラブル アイ フェイス
Before I knew, it withers way too soon, that one word that rings true
在我知晓之前语言已然枯萎
何時しか言の葉は疾うに枯れきって
ビフォー アイ ニュー イット ウィザーズ ウェイ トゥー スーン ザット ワン ワード ザット リングス トゥルー
And now, a fruit will bloom in my heart I can't move
而现在一颗果实将无可改变地在我心中绽放
事の実があたしに熟れている
アンド ナウ ア フルーツ ウィル ブルーム イン マイ ハート アイ キャント ムーブ
Within the mirror's sight, there's a painting inside
在镜子的另一侧 有一副画将我描绘
鏡に映り嘘を描いて
ウィズイン ザ ミラーズ サイト ゼアズ ア ペインティング インサイド
A sign of "make up" lighting the loss in my life
它所映出的“虚伪”将我的失意照亮
自らを見失なった絵画
ア サイン オブ メイクアップ ライティング ザ ロス イン マイ ライフ
パラッパラパパパパパパ
pa ra ppa ra pa pa pa pa pa pa
Let's play this game
让我们开始这场游戏吧
謎々
レッツ プレイ ディス ゲーム
Where we count the riddles that we made
在那里 我们细数着我们制造的谎言
かぞえて遊びましょう
ウェア ウィー カウント ザ リドルズ ザット ウィー メイド
ダラッダダダダダラッダッダ
da ra dda da da da da ra dda dda
Why stay? Why stay?
为何被困于此？为何停滞不前？
何故何故
ホワイ ステイ ホワイ ステイ
In this place and dance the night away?
为何要在这里起舞直至天明呢？
此処で踊っているでしょう
イン ディス プレイス アンド ダンス ザ ナイト アウェイ
I just can't see the simple things I can't keep
连那些简单的事情也搞不明白
簡単なことも解らないわ
アイ ジャスト キャント シー ザ シンプル シングズ アイ キャント キープ
What am I supposed to be?
这样的我到底算什么？
あたしって何だっけ
ワット アム アイ サポーズド トゥ ビー
Shaken by the hand of night, it seems stirring in a dream
被夜的手掌所包裹 仿佛在梦中激荡
それすら夜の手に絆されて
シェイクン バイ ザ ハンド オブ ナイト イット シームズ スターリング イン ア ドリーム
Like your love for me
如同你给予我的爱
愛のように
ライク ユア ラブ フォー ミー
Its leaving its leaving
它在消失 它在离去
消える 消える
イッツ リーヴィング イッツ リーヴィング
I would cry and weep without a "bye" as I grieve
及时悲伤至极 也未曾说出“再见”
さようならも言えぬ儘 泣いた
アイ ラッド クライ アンド ウィープ ウィズアウト ア バイ アズ アイ グリーブ
PHONY PHONY PHONY
虚伪 虚伪 虚伪
フォニイフォニイフォニイ
フォニー フォニー フォニー
Still tangled up in lies, I see I'm just a fake, phony
仍被困于谎言之中 我明白我只是个虚像 一个虚伪的人
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニイ
スティル タングルド アップ イン ライズ アイ シー アイム ジャスト ア フェイク フォニー
Antipathy world
这个令人厌恶的世界
アンティパシー ワールド
Before I knew the sky, so very blue, joined an ugly old tune
在我知晓天空的蔚蓝之前 它就被丑陋的老调所污染
何時しかそらの音がいやに鳴り合って
ビフォー アイ ニュー ザ スカイ ソー ベリー ブルー ジョインド アン アグリー オールド チューン
My colored view of you breaks away what you do
透过有色眼镜看着你 你所做的一切都令人厌恶
色の目があなたを溶いている
マイ カラード ビュー オブ ユー ブレイクス アウェイ ホワット ユー ドゥー
Within the mirror's sight, there, I'm missing inside
在镜子的另一侧 我的倒影已然无踪
鏡に映るあたしを欠いて
ウィズイン ザ ミラーズ サイト ゼア アイム ミッシング インサイド
There lies a "fake" that's hiding the truth they can't find
只有一个“赝品”隐藏着不为人知的真相
誰しもが見間違った
ゼア ライズ ア フェイク ザッツ ハイディング ザ トゥルース ゼイ キャント ファインド
I say, why live and stay
我说啊 为什么要留在这里
如何して愛なんて
アイ セイ ホワイ リブ アンド ステイ
Where every body craves that thing known as love that will only bring us pain?
为何每个人都渴望着爱 而爱只会带来痛苦？
ものに群がりそれを欲して生きるのだ
ウェア エヴリ バディ クレイヴズ ザット シング ノウン アズ ラブ ザット ウィル オンリー ブリング アス ペイン
I play and swim today as I am left behind in every way by the train
我又若无其事地度过了一天 仿佛是列车弃我而去
今日も泳いでいる夜の電車が通り去っていく
アイ プレイ アンド スウィム トゥデイ アズ アイ アム レフト ビハインド イン エヴリ ウェイ バイ ザ トレイン
So dance the night away and
舞蹈着直到天明吧
踊り明かせよ
ソー ダンス ザ ナイト アウェイ アンド
パパラッパパパパパパ
pa pa ra ppa pa pa pa pa pa
We meant pretense
我们用着谎言 伪装者自己
謎々
ウィー メント プリテンス
As we sang with riddles in the end
讴歌者虚伪 行向末路
騙して歌いましょう
アズ ウィー サング ウィズ リドルズ イン ジ エンド
ダラッダダダダダラッダッダ
da ra dda da da da da ra dda dda
Why then, why then does it hurt so much right here again?
为什么 为什么 为什么那里又在隐隐作痛呢
何故何故此処が痛むのでしょう
ホワイ ゼン ホワイ ゼン ダズ イット ハート ソー マッチ ライト ヒア アゲイン
ダッダラッダッダラッダッダララッダダララダッダラッダンダダララーラ
da dda ra dda dda ra dda dda ra ra dda da ra ra da dda ra ddan da da ra ra a ra
ダレンダラッダラッラッダララッダッダダッダラッダッダダッラッダーラララ
da ren da ra dda ra rra dda ra ra dda dda da dda ra dda dda da rra dda a ra ra ra
I just can't change the days I only feel pain
我无法改变那些让我感到痛苦的日子
散々な日々は変わらないわ
アイ ジャスト キャント チェンジ ザ デイズ アイ オンリー フィール ペイン
I can't escape this wave of limitless rain
我无法逃离这场永无止境的雨
絶望の雨は止まないわ
アイ キャント エスケイプ ディス ウェイヴ オブ リミットレス レイン
I would cry and weep without a "bye" as I grieve
即使悲伤至极 也未曾说出“再见”
さようならも言えぬ儘 泣いた
アイ ラッド クライ アンド ウィープ ウィズアウト ア バイ アズ アイ グリーブ
PHONY PHONY PHONY
虚伪 虚伪 虚伪
フォニイフォニイフォニイ
フォニー フォニー フォニー
Still tangled up in lies, I see you leave
仍被困于谎言之中 我注视着你离去的方向
嘘に絡まっている　ただ
スティル タングルド アップ イン ライズ アイ シー ユー リーブ
I just can't see the simple things I can't keep
连那些简单的事情也搞不明白
簡単なことも解らないわ
アイ ジャスト キャント シー ザ シンプル シングズ アイ キャント キープ
What I am supposed to be?
这样的我 到底算什么
あたしって何だっけ
ワット アイ アム サポーズド トゥ ビー
Shaken by the hand of night, it seems stirring in a dream
被夜的手掌所包裹 仿佛在梦中激荡
それすら夜の手に絆されて
シェイクン バイ ザ ハンド オブ ナイト イット シームズ スターリング イン ア ドリーム
Like your love for me
如同你给予我的爱
愛のように
ライク ユア ラブ フォー ミー
Its leaving its leaving
它在消失 它在离去
イッツ リーヴィング イッツ リーヴィング
消える 消える
I would sigh and breathe a little "bye" as I grieve
即使悲伤至极 也仅是发出一声叹息 我说着“再见”
さようならまたねと呟いた
アイ ラッド サイ アンド ブリーズ ア リトル バイ アズ アイ グリーブ
PHONY PHONY PHONY
虚伪 虚伪 虚伪
フォニイフォニイフォニイ
フォニー フォニー フォニー
Still tangled up in lies, I see I'm just a fake, phony
仍被困于谎言之中 我明白我只是个虚像 一个虚伪的人
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニイ
スティル タングルド アップ イン ライズ アイ シー アイム ジャスト ア フェイク フォニー
Just flowers that deceive, they keep this secret, fake, phony
就像假花一样的把戏 他们守护着秘密、假象和虚伪
造花だけが知っている秘密のフォニイ
ジャスト フラワーズ ザット ディシーヴ ゼイ キープ ディス シークレット フェイク フォニー